# **MOHANAD AL-SAMANEH**

Confident and reliable IT support engineer with extensive practical experience of working with computers and resolving any support issues that are raised to the service desk.

**P**ossessing a proven ability to administer and control the operation, configuration and maintenance of computer based information systems, as well as having an eye for detail and able to multi-task under pressure.

Obtaining a powerful knowledge on Linux OS and Command Line.

I work well alone or in a group and also have experience managing groups.

**Nationality:** Jordanian Contact number: +905388774060 Email: MohanadLinux@gmail.com Date of Birth: Aug.30.1983 Marital status: Single

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Al Qusaily Building LLC AD, UAE

IT support technician Dec2014 - Oct2020

- Install authorised software to laptops and desktops
- Providing Maintenance Support and break-fix solutions

#### **ICapital AD, UAE**

Support Engineer Mar2013 - Oct2014

- Support Engineer on MOH System (Ministry of Health - Cerner)
- Maintenance Support
- Diagnose and resolve technical issue

### Mideast Data Systems LLC AD, UAE

Support Engineer Jul2010 - Jan2013

- Installing PC and Imaging
- Hardware Installation and Configuration

#### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

Oracle University KIC,

Oracle Database 10g

AD, UAE

May 2009

SQI

Creating an Oracle Database

Managing Table spaces and Data files

Administration Users

Oracle Database Security & Monitoring

Managing Shared Servers

Logical and Physical (Backup & Recovery)

Recovery Manager (RMAN).

## Ovidius University, Constanta, Romania

**BachelorDegree** in Mathematics and computer science 2008

## Abu Dhabi secondary school, AD, UAE

Certificate of high school Scientific stream 2001

#### **SKILLS**

#### LANGUAGES

**Systems:** Cerner (health care system),

Oracle Database 10a

Device Maintenance: A+

Networking: Network+, CCNA Operating Systems: Win, Linux

**Programming Languages:** 

Python, PHP&MySQL, SQL, HTML & CSS

Key skills: MS Office, LibreOffice

Arabic Enalish Romanian